<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PcSetCalc</string>
    <string name="_0">0</string>
    <string name="_1">1</string>
    <string name="_2">2</string>
    <string name="_3">3</string>
    <string name="_4">4</string>
    <string name="_5">5</string>
    <string name="_6">6</string>
    <string name="_7">7</string>
    <string name="_8">8</string>
    <string name="_9">9</string>
    <string name="_A">A</string>
    <string name="_B">B</string>
    <string name="clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="normal_form">Normal Form</string>
    <string name="prime_form">Prime Form</string>
    <string name="interval_vector">Interval Vector</string>
    <string name="forte_number">Forte Number</string>
    <string name="transposition">Tn</string>
    <string name="inversion">In</string>
    <string name="undo">Undo</string>
    <string name="no_value">---</string>
    <string name="prime_form_key">Prime\nForm</string>
    <string name="forte_number_key">Forte\nNumber</string>
    <string name="interval_vector_key">Interval\nVector</string>
    <string name="tn_sym_key">Tn\nsym.</string>
    <string name="in_sym_key">In\nsym.</string>
    <string name="rate_the_app">Play Store page</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="t_e_preference_title">T and E instead of A and B</string>
    <string name="t_e_preference_summary">Turning this on changes all instances of pitch-class 10
        and 11 to be labelled T and E, respectively, instead of the default A and B</string>
    <string name="forte_algorithm_preference_title">Forte\'s algorithm instead of Rahn\'s</string>
    <string name="forte_algorithm_preference_summary">Enable Forte\'s algorithm to be used when
        calculating PC set data. This only affects set classes 5&#45;20, 6&#45;Z29, 6&#45;31,
        7&#45;20, and 8&#45;26</string>
    <string name="about_normal_form_title">Normal Form</string>
    <string name="about_prime_form_title">Prime Form</string>
    <string name="about_interval_vector_title">Interval(-class) Vector</string>
    <string name="about_forte_number_title">Forte Number</string>
    <string name="about_normal_form_desc">
        A pitch-class set can be presented musically in a variety of ways. Conversely, many
different musical figures can represent the same pitch-class set. If we want to be able
to recognize a pitch-class set no matter how it is presented in the music, it will be
helpful to put it into a simple, compact, easily grasped form called the normal form.
The normal form—the most compressed way of writing a pitch-class set—makes it
easy to see the essential attributes of a set and to compare it to other sets.
    </string>
    <string name="about_prime_form_desc">
        A common way of identifying set classes is to look at all of the
members of the set class, select the one with the \"most normal\" of normal forms, and
use that to name the set class as a whole. This optimal form, called the prime form,
begins with 0 and is most packed to the left.
    </string>
    <string name="about_interval_vector_desc">
        Interval-class content is usually presented as a string of six numbers with no spaces
intervening. This is called an interval-class vector. The first number in an interval-
class vector gives the number of occurrences of interval class 1; the second gives
the number of occurrences of interval class 2; and so on.\n\n
        We can construct a vector like this for sonorities of any size or shape. A tool
like the interval-class vector would not be nearly so necessary for talking about
traditional tonal music. There, only a few basic sonorities—four kinds of triads and five
kinds of seventh chords—are regularly in use. In post-tonal music, however, we will
confront a huge variety of harmonies. The interval-class vector will give us a
convenient way of summarizing their basic sound.
    </string>

    <string name="about_forte_number_desc">
        A standard way of naming set classes was devised by the theorist
Allen Forte, who pioneered the theory of pitch-class sets. On his well-known list of set
classes, he identifies each with a pair of numbers separated by a dash (e.g., 3&#45;4). The
first number tells the number of pitch classes in the set. The second number gives the
position of the set on Forte\'s list. Set class 3&#45;4, for example, is the fourth set on Forte\'s
list of three-note sets.
    </string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="about_credits_text">Each of these descriptions were taken from Joseph N. Straus\'
        \"Introduction to Post-Tonal Theory,\" 3rd edition. Thanks, Joe.</string>
    <string name="about_symmetry_title">
        Transpositional and Inversional Symmetry
    </string>
    <string name="about_symmetry_desc">
        There is a small handful of sets that, like the whole-tone scale, are capable of
mapping entirely onto themselves under transposition. Sets with that capacity are said to
be transpositionally symmetrical. If the interval-class vector contains an entry equal
to the number of notes in the set (or half that number in the case of the tritone), then
the set has this property. \n\n
        Some set classes contain sets that can map entirely onto themselves under inversion.
Such set classes are said to be inversionally symmetrical and, of the 208 set classes
listed in this app, seventy-nine have this property. The index vector for a set with
this property will have an entry equal to the number of notes in the set.\n\n
        Sets that are inversionally symmetrical can be written so that the intervals
reading from left to right are the same as the intervals reading from right to left. Usually,
but not always, this intervallic palindrome will be apparent when the set is written in
normal form. Occasionally, a note has to be written twice to capture the modular
wraparound.
    </string>
</resources>
